pakpoint.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy

This privacy policy is applicable to pakpoint.com, pakpoint.net and pakpoint.org

We do not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information will be gathered from the registration process for a web site or other services we may offer. Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties. Further, we reserves the right to contact a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected.

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of our internet servers or through the use of â€œcookies.â€ â€œCookiesâ€ are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the userâ€™s ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a userâ€™s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain

The foregoing policies are effective as of March 1, 2009. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**

© 2012 PakPoint Network. Disclaimer: PakPoint Network trust on the freedom of expression. All the material, videos, images and links posted here are contributed by the members of the site or taken from third party websites and/or are already in public domain and are owned by their respective rightful owners. We do not record or sell any copyrighted material. All trademarks, trade names, service marks, copyrighted work, logos referenced herein belong to their respective owners/companies. If you find any content in violation of your rights please give your feedback and it will be removed immediately. pakpoint @ gmail.com
